♪ There is a taste of peace ♪
♪ Every night we dance in my dreams ♪
♪ The cupid's an archer ♪
♪ His violent departure ♪
♪ Leaves us at the altar ♪
♪ Wounded, weak and ready to bleed ♪
Sing it, girl.
Mom. Now I can't.
Her spontaneity
has been stripped from her.
I'm sorry.
You have such a beautiful voice.
I can't wait to hear it
when you're older.
Will this place have scuba diving?
How old does a child have to be
to do scuba diving?
I don't know, Trent.
- I think you're a bit too young.
- You're a baby.
You said five minutes. Technically,
it's been way, way more than five minutes.
Are we close?
Stop wishing away this moment.
Look out the window,
look how pretty it is.
Prisca.
Work stuff?
Yeah.
Lead by actions, Mom.
Wow.
This is much better than Cancún.
Mr. and Mrs. Capa,
welcome to our version of paradise.
Wow.
Hello!
So, this is Madrid.
She'll take care of you.
From your food and beverage preferences
you selected,
we've made you cocktails to welcome you.
Wow.
- Thank you.
- Look how big you guys are.
We have a drink fountain for you two.
- Can we go?
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- Let's go, let's go.
Can you believe I found this online?
It's gorgeous.
My favorite thing,
open 24 hours,
the candy station.
Oh, my God. Come on, Trent.
Mix the vanilla and strawberry in it.
Say hi, Trent.
Hi.
I'm Idlib.
My uncle's the resort manager here.
He's Trent, I'm Maddox.
I can do a thousand-piece jigsaw puzzle,
which is a considerable thing to do.
My dad and I put clear glue on them
and then hang them on my wall.
I collect conch shells.
I have 42 conch shells.
Amazing.
- I might need a little help with this.
- Okay.
Right, so you do strawberry and vanilla?
Hi.
Thank you. Yes.
Okay.
Okay, I got it. Okay, come on.
Thank you. Heh.
Great job helping. Yes.
- You!
- I touched your jacket, that...
Hey!
There's 250,000 furniture-related injuries
in the United States per year.
25% of those, coffee table injuries.
Hey. Hey!
- Fine.
- Okay.
Warren and Warren
must be affiliated with this resort.
They must have conventions here.
We love this pharmaceutical company
at work.
We're considering asking our clients
to use Warren and Warren drugs
as a way to lower their insurance rates.
Ah. Hmm. Yeah.
"No kids allowed on the beach"?
What? Hold on.
- "No Kids Week"?
- That's not true! Let me see that!
It says no ki...
Prisca, you should've checked.
- Let me see that!
- It's your mom's fault.
No, really, no. It says this, no...
- Let me see!
- She should've checked. It says this.
- Yes, of course.
I know this is
very painful news for you all to bear.
But now, now I've got the power.
Yes! And you have to do it.
Yeah, you have to understand.
It's like this.
- Daddy!
- Life is like this.
It's tough and sometimes
it doesn't go the way you want it to.
Come on! Blue team is winning.
What's your name
and what do you do for a living?
Hey, guys. I'm Annette. What's your name?
I'm Trent. This is Idlib.
Hey, nice to meet you.
- Bye.
Bye.
Hi, I'm Trent. This is Idlib.
What are your names,
and what do you do for a living?
Well, I'm Sophia Watson.
I'm a chef.
I'm Greg Mitchell. I'm a cop.
Cool.
And I'm Malin Mitchell. I'm a dancer.
Wow. That's cool.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- Hey, let's go over there.
Come on, let's go over there.
Truth-telling game. Go.
I can't do a push-up. Go.
I don't have friends.
I'm your friend.
You'll leave.
My mom might let me FaceTime you.
Then we can be friends.
You can come over to my house
and make up stories.
Then we can go to
the same college together
and become neighbors with mortgages.
Cool.
It's weird.
I know.
It's hanging over me. I can barely eat.
And I don't feel anything?
We agreed.
We'd give them one last vacation
before telling them.
I can't understand
why we don't take into consideration...
That shouldn't affect anything.
The doctor said it's a non-factor.
It's probably been there for years,
he said.
We were on a course to separate.
That's confusing enough for us.
Let's not bring an irrelevant
medical condition into this.
Let's get through this, Guy.
Compartmentalize.
It's only for three days.
You found a place?
Yes.
Oh, Prisca. Come on.
You're always thinking about the future!
It makes me feel not seen!
You're always thinking
about the past.
You work in a goddamn museum!
I think they stopped.
Why don't you play?
Good morning.
What would you like for breakfast?
I'll have the Calcium Bomb juice drink.
I have a calcium deficiency.
So, is it really calcium rich
or just a catchy name?
It has all calcium-rich vegetables, ma'am.
- Sit up, Kara, honey.
- Okay.
You don't wanna be hunched
when you grow up, baby.
It's very unattractive.
Boys will get turned off.
Give me the Calcium Bomb juice.
And maybe you could
recommend one of these.
This one.
I recommend the granola parfait.
It's a good choice.
Okay.
So, how is the Capa family?
Any plans today?
Well, one of our kids
wants to do Jet Ski.
And the other one
wants to do anything but that.
Aha.
Well, there's, um...
there's a private beach
on the nature preserve side of the island.
It's impossible to find.
It's surrounded by stunning rocks,
very unusual minerals.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
A natural anomaly.
I only recommend it to certain guests.
But I liked you guys immediately.
All right?
You're a nice family.
So I could arrange a van to take you, if...
Yeah.
Sounds like a great memory for us.
It's our little secret.
I'll make all the arrangements.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
Okay, so I think we should get
the Calloway Kale-away for Trent.
Idlib, what did I tell you about
being in here when you shouldn't?
You can't...
You know, I told you so many times.
You know, we have certain rules...
I'm a doctor.
My wife has epilepsy.
I'm a nurse. My name is Jarin.
Right, she's having a grand mal seizure.
Keep things away from her, please.
Patricia?
Doll.
Jack, I think if you just
leave her lying here for a while,
put something under her head.
I think she'll be fine.
Thank you, Doctor.
It's Jarin, by the way.
For my next act,
I'll spin my head around 360.
I'm sorry I ruined everyone's breakfast.
You always want to be
the center of attention.
My goodness.
Let's get you something to drink?
Yeah.
Idlib.
Can't be that secret a beach.
We were told to keep it quiet.
- So were we.
- Sit down, Gustav. Good boy.
Good boy. Stay.
Okay, guest checklist.
Books, sunscreen.
Did everybody
leave their passports in their safes?
- I don't want anybody to lose anything.
- Yeah.
What are your names and occupations?
It's very rocky here.
Okay, my friends.
You can just call us,
and we'll pick you up
whenever you're ready to come back.
Or I'll pick you up at 5:00 p.m.
Just follow the path down to the beach.
- Is that also food?
- Yeah.
Wow, that's a lot of food.
Well, kids eat a lot of food.
And you got three of them with you.
Okay.
Seems like a waste,
but thank you.
Could you help us
carry some of these bags, please?
We've got an elderly person here
and a child.
I'm sorry. I gotta get back.
But it's not far.
Just walk down.
You'll see a beautiful slot canyon.
Walk through that, and in a few minutes,
you'll be there. Enjoy, everybody!
- Do you think there's...
- Come on.
- Do you think there's snakes?
- Of course.
Cool. I wanna see one.
- Gorgeous.
- Wow.
Okay.
You okay? Yeah?
Could someone please
tell me what just happened?
Look out.
- This is so exciting!
- Careful now.
- Let's go!
- I'm gonna win!
Whoo!
Wow. I just got chills.
Come on, darling.
Let's show Gustav the sea.
Hey, Maddox, help your mom.
Listen, I... Let's move somewhere else.
I think it's much nicer
closer to the water, right?
- Yeah, but I...
- No, it's... Look. It's beautiful.
I got you!
Have you ever
seen anything like that?
They were right to send us.
Lie down.
Yeah. Good boy!
Kids, look at the beautiful coral.
- What are you going to do?
- Now I'm gonna splash you.
Just keep on reading, I guess.
You just splashed me.
Stop! I didn't mean you could splash me.
Guy?
Yeah.
What book am I reading?
I don't know.
Why?
No reason.
Prisca,
I wanted to tell you something.
No, never mind.
I'll tell you later.
Oh, my God.
That's Mid-Sized Sedan.
What? Mid what?
He's a rapper!
"More Dough for the Cookin" '?
- Mid-Sized Sedan?
- Let's begin an activity.
Dad, I have to, okay? I have to!
- No. Leave him. Because it's a private...
- Sounds like fun.
- But, Dad, stop! I need to say hi.
- He's on vacation, he's on vacation.
What's his surname? Sedan?
Whoo!
Oh!
Whoa, all right.
Here's a big one. Wow.
Help me with this.
We should have a housewarming party.
Isn't our house so beautiful?
- Boo!
- Aah! You!
- Come! Come back here!
- No!
Not gonna get me!
Kara, you know,
I'm gonna get you right now.
Come on.
Not gonna get me!
Oh, I am.
Come on, Kara.
Oh!
Oh, my God. Got you.
You're never gonna catch me.
Honey, I'm home.
I told you, I don't wanna live like this.
I'm gonna live in a condominium.
I'm going for a drive to calm down.
I'm really, really hungry.
Me, too. My stomach's growling.
Me, too.
Wow.
Who would leave this?
Hey, Mom!
From the hotel.
They're so rusted.
Put that down!
You can get infected
or you'll cut yourself!
Come away.
Next activity.
- What's happening?
- Let's play hide-and-seek.
I don't know. They found stuff
from the hotel in the sand.
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
- No fish.
- Ready or not, here we come!
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
- What is it? What is it?
- Trent!
Someone over there.
Over there.
Come on. Give me a hand. Get the legs.
Yes.
- Make your list. Make your list.
- Okay.
Red and orange.
Red, orange. Come away from here, babies.
Let the doctor try and help this lady.
Yeah?
- Green.
- Tan.
- Purple.
- What happened?
- It's okay.
Blue. Blue is good. And then?
- Green.
- Green, yes.
- Yellow. Purple.
- Yellow. I love yellow.
Call the police, right?
I'll get my mobile.
Oh, damn.
What happened to her, Mom?
I don't know.
I'm still hungry.
Me, too.
Was she with you?
I was waiting for her.
She swam out by herself, yo.
I don't know what the hell happened.
I ain't saying nothing else.
Did you strike him?
I don't need to know the context of...
What? No. Of course not.
So why's your nose bleeding?
I told y'all,
I ain't got nothing to say to you.
My chest feels funny.
Well, you know, we should've
gotten a yacht like I suggested, Agnes.
You shouldn't have fought me on that.
You see? Now we're mixed up
in some island issue.
I mean, I...
Mom, my swimsuit is hurting.
I have to take it off.
Well, just loosen your...
We're from Philadelphia.
I'm on a break here
with my wife and kids. That's them.
Well, yeah, over there.
And for the record,
I know most people who die on vacation
die from sun exposure, overexertion,
overindulgence of food or alcohol,
or a mixture of all of the above
99.4% of the time.
- How you know all this?
- I'm an actuary.
I calculate people's insurance rates
based on their risk profile.
I ain't do nothing, man.
She was into me.
Somebody will figure this out.
We'll just have to wait
for them to get here.
No reception at all.
I guess our beach day's over.
We've gotta keep an eye on him
and the body.
Whoo!
Oh, my goodness.
Wow.
Did you just get dropped off
by the resort?
Yeah. We were supposed to come earlier,
but we rested in the room first.
Great. We have to get the resort people
before they leave.
I think we will all
have to leave this beach.
Wait. Why? They left already.
What happened?
We really don't know what happened.
Well, I think this man
had something to do with it.
Man, if I was involved, why would I
be standing around, bro? Damn.
His nose is bleeding. I think he got that
when she was trying to defend herself.
I don't like this dynamic at all.
My nose has been bleeding for hours, man.
I don't know why it's doing that.
Charles, something's wrong with
your mother. She's asking for you, honey.
Well, we're all in this now.
We are responsible for that woman.
And I've got nothing against this man.
I'm just doing what needs to be done.
No cell phone reception
on this beach.
You stay here.
I'll go to the clearing in the jungle
where they dropped us and try to call.
They obviously have a signal out here.
How else do people call to go back?
Oh, my God.
You stumbled back out,
you were holding your head.
You looked like you were in pain, babe.
You blacked out.
I felt this pressure in my head.
I'm fine, Charles.
I think it's the shock.
Try to help Gustav or he'll be sick.
Yeah, of course it's the shock.
I'm gonna get a van
to take us back to the resort,
but first I've got to deal
with all this, all right?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I know you've been stressed.
Don't let this upset you.
Help these people through this, Charles.
So, what did you hear?
Excuse me.
I saw you were talking to my husband.
I know you're dealing with a lot
with that woman right now,
but something is wrong with my son.
Some kind of reaction.
Is it severe? I don't have time for this.
What kind of doctor are you?
I'm a cardiothoracic surgeon
and chief medical officer.
You don't know me.
I curate exhibits for museums.
I'm telling you this
because I want you to trust me
and not think I'm being hysterical
when I say
there's something very wrong
with my child.
He seems fine to me.
He's playing with my daughter.
You look different, too.
How?
Huh? I don't know.
You just look different.
Hold my hand.
Okay.
Willow, Japanese maple.
- Evergreen.
- If you get scared, just tell me, okay?
What do you keep looking at?
- There.
- Where?
Way, way up there
on the side of the hillside.
What do you see?
I thought I saw something shiny.
Here comes Mom.
Charles!
She stopped breathing!
I didn't do anything, Charles.
You guys, you just walked away,
and she just stopped breathing
all of a sudden.
I mean, she was peaceful.
Can you step back, please?
We'll take the kids
away from here.
Is this happening?
She couldn't take the shock.
She saw a murdered woman
and her heart couldn't take it.
What are your names
and occupations?
I'm Jarin. I'm a nurse.
I'm Patricia. I'm a psychologist.
He remembers everyone's names
and things about them.
Everything's gonna be okay.
What's your name?
I'm Trent.
This is my sister, Maddox.
How old are you guys?
I'll guess. I'm good at this.
You're 11, right, Trent?
I'm six.
No. Really, are you 10, 11?
He's not lying. He's six.
I'm specifically six and a quarter.
She's 11.
They're feeling unsafe.
There is a lot going on here.
They're playing with us. Let's leave it.
Okay, what's your best friend's name?
Maddox.
How sweet.
Have you seen my children?
Is everyone trying to play a joke on us?
- What?
- Aren't these your children?
I'm right here, Mom.
Mom?
Mom.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Prisca, I think we should leave.
Get the kids back to the resort.
Guy...
- Maddox?
- Yeah. Dad, it's me.
What's going on?
You see? You see?
Holy...
Damn.
- How did we get here?
- Take it easy.
Intense cranial pressure.
It's like being deep underwater.
- I can't...
- Can you get up?
Whoa. Whoa. Take it easy.
Charles?
- Yeah, no, I'm all right. I'm fine.
- You okay?
We're leaving right now,
and we're taking our kids.
For some reason,
people are blacking out going this way.
Three people have blacked out now.
- That's ridiculous. Come, move.
- No, I saw it, Prisca.
I saw Jarin black out.
What I know is that we have to get
these kids to a hospital. Now.
Look, let's stop talking about it.
The kids are scared.
I can stay here with them.
But everyone else should try and find
a different pathway off this beach.
Break off into groups of two
in case people black out.
Chrystal, go with me.
- Okay.
- Whatever you do, just stay close.
I'm feeling very uncomfortable right now.
Don't get up too quickly.
Kids, let Mom and Dad talk for a second.
No. Mom, we're scared.
Please. Stay right here.
Okay?
- If I cry, please don't let them see.
- I won't.
- Your hands are shaking.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they are.
Yeah. You okay?
We're on a beach
with two unrelated dead bodies.
That is just statistically impossible.
All three kids are reacting to something.
Only the kids.
I mean, look at the doctor's daughter.
The kids are reacting
to something they ate.
Or they caught something.
We're on a remote, undeveloped island,
but we have a doctor here.
So, let's get the doctor
to look at the kids.
I still can't get any reception.
Doctor, before we do anything else,
can you take a look
at our children, please?
Oh!
He's got a knife!
There's a damn hole in my cheek!
- Oh, my God! Are you okay?
- Put that down right now, Doctor.
Watch out, Jarin.
Listen, I don't know why I did that.
I thought he was gonna hurt me.
Sorry.
- Sorry.
- What's he talking about, "sorry"?
- Let me see that laceration.
- That's assault, man!
Calm down.
What's your name?
Mid-Sized Sedan.
I must be in shock. I'm numb.
I'm not feeling the pain no more.
Please. Let me see.
No, this is not making any sense, Prisca.
I need to get my ass to a hospital now.
What's with all y'all faces?
It's hard to explain.
This is messed up, man.
Where'd it go?
This is some kind of parlor trick.
Yo, I know
I tried to dip, but I am freaked, man.
I just wanna go back to my hotel room.
This was supposed to be a zen trip, man.
She and I only started talking
because she was sick, and so am I.
She had just been diagnosed with MS,
so we started rapping about that.
I didn't do nothing to that girl, man.
She was like Michael Phelps
swimming out there,
backstroking and whatnot.
She swam way the hell out.
What did you say?
No, I don't know, man.
Maybe it was butterfly stroke.
I don't watch the Summer Olympics
like that.
You came vacationing here
because you were sick,
- and so did she?
- I thought that was a cool coincidence.
Maybe this is some kind of
group psychosis. I've studied this.
We're all emotionally shaky
from our lives.
We don't believe
we can leave this beach.
Mom.
Is there any more food?
I'm still hungry.
- Well, she's definitely aged.
- How can you still be hungry? We just...
I'd put her biological age
somewhere between 12 and 13,
and she turned six
two weeks ago on Tuesday.
What?
We're older?
Am I okay?
I don't know what's happening
to the three of you, sweetheart.
But for now,
I have another swimsuit in my bag,
and maybe you should change into that.
It might be a virus, maybe.
Could be mosquitoes where...
The way they behave
on this part of the island.
Something's happening to her
that's triggering her hormones.
The dog has died!
- Oh, my God.
He was only just alive.
- Kara, hold on to me, baby.
- What's happening?
Who thinks they can swim
a hundred lengths of a pool
against currents,
and then turn and swim
an unknown amount along the coast
till we find another shore?
That's what I'm guessing the distance is
to swim out and get around this cove.
It looks too far. Babe, it's not safe.
My name is Brendon.
I went to private school.
My mom is an attorney,
and my dad is a dentist.
- Yo, I just wanted somebody to know that.
- Okay.
I have a problem with my blood.
A rare issue with its clotting.
I came to this island to see the ocean
and remember I'm connected
to something bigger.
That's beautiful, Brendon.
I don't feel the same way
I felt yesterday or this morning,
and I don't think
my parents would understand.
My thoughts have more colors in them now.
Yesterday, I had a few colors
and they were really strong,
and now I have more and they're quieter.
Okay!
Everyone, gather!
Come on, come on, come on!
Everyone needs to have a voice here.
Are you sure we have time for this?
We will make destructive decisions
if we don't feel safe with each other.
I know we don't have time,
but why don't we start with you two?
Why are you here?
- We've been having a tough time...
- Chrystal.
We've been going through something.
He's under a lot of stress as a doctor.
He needed some time away.
Everyone does.
I'm not unusual in that.
Charles, it's okay.
I'm not gonna say anything else.
Good! It's nice to hear from you both.
How about you guys?
Prisca?
It's nothing.
We just have to make a decision.
The kids are reacting to something.
It's a virus. It's probably a virus.
I just need to catch my breath.
I just started feeling weird a minute ago.
Are you okay, Mom?
- Mom?
- What's wrong?
Are you okay, Mom?
I don't think it's the...
- She has a tumor.
- What?
But it's benign.
They said it's benign.
Oh, my God.
Mom?
Is it... Where?
- Mom?
- It's okay.
Can I...
I can feel it.
It's the size of a golf ball.
No, it's supposed to be
three centimeters.
All right. Let me see.
- Whoa! Prisca!
- Mom!
- She's gonna faint.
- Prisca.
Mom.
- Let her get some air!
- Wake up, Pris. Don't do this.
It's there.
It's been there for a while.
It's the size of a softball.
Jesus.
- It's grown.
- What?
- What's happening to Mom?
- What's going on?
- Dad! Dad, what's happening to Mom?
- It's okay.
Trent, why don't you two guys go play
somewhere else on the beach, okay? Okay?
Mom's a little bit tired.
Would you do that for me, tiger?
The first adult
is being affected.
What if we cut it out?
- Dad!
- Not possible.
Actually, it is. But it's Guy's call.
No! No, no, no! No!
I don't wanna make this decision.
No. No, I...
I don't know what to do.
- Do we have alcohol?
- Yes.
Some bottles from the minibar.
I cannot be held responsible.
You understand?
Yes.
Okay. Well, does anyone
have a needle and thread?
- We have to sew this up.
- Yeah, yeah. Uh...
Here. Here. Is this the right decision?
- Maybe we should all talk about this.
- I can't think.
This tumor is going to kill her.
Did you know that Jack Nicholson
did a film with Marlon Brando?
Oh, no.
What is he saying?
- What was the name of that film?
- Charles, breathe.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Will you let me do my job, please?
- Is he okay?
Cut her again.
We'll keep our hands in there
to keep the incision open.
Guy, I can help, brother.
No, I'll take care of her.
Does anyone know the name of that film?
It was with Jack Nicholson
and Marlon Brando.
- Both.
- Try again, Doctor.
Oblique incision on the side of the belly,
four to six inches. You can do this.
Put your fingers inside the incision.
Okay.
Can you open it
a little wider, please?
It's closing around my fingers.
Keep pulling it apart. That's it.
I'm lifting the tumor out.
Wow! It's the size of a cantaloupe!
Wait!
It's attached to something.
- Muscle tissue.
- Okay.
Could you hold the incision open
a little wider, if you would?
I'm so sorry, Pris.
Just cutting underneath the tumor.
Okay. Got it.
Mom.
Prisca?
Mom?
It's okay.
I just fainted.
We took the tumor out.
It was going to kill you.
Your husband made a fast decision.
Guy, I feel better.
Damn!
Come on, y'all, look at this!
Hurry!
Damn.
Come on, y'all!
Can we all agree I didn't do that?
What happened to her?
The body has decomposed.
- How quickly can that happen?
- A long time.
Mom knows this stuff.
I'm not a forensic pathologist,
but from excavations for the museum,
I know that it varies
based on soil and temperature.
My best guess, an exposed body,
the flesh will be gone
in approximately seven years.
And this happened in, what,
three hours?
I know.
And bones, we've found,
will disintegrate in 30 years more.
What the hell, man?
On this beach, less than 20 hours
after you die, you just return to dust.
What exactly are we saying?
Something is going on
with time on this beach.
Time?
You have wrinkles.
I'm scared.
It's best to focus on specifics
in the present in unsettling situations.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like breathing.
What's happening to us?
Are we sick, too?
No, I don't think so.
I think we're just growing.
Going by Trent and Maddox's ages
and the time we spent on this beach,
half an hour is equivalent
to something like one year of our lives.
This must be true for all of us,
we just don't see it on everyone.
It's the first time
they wished they were Black.
Mm-hmm.
The kids are eating so much
because their mass is growing.
They need to grow
an enormous amount of mass quickly.
We're staying roughly the same mass.
Our cells are just aging.
I don't feel the same.
It's like my mind is changing, too.
I'm getting many thoughts
at the same time.
It's weird.
I'm not as scared
about what's happening to us.
What about our hair and nails?
Shouldn't they be growing
at an abnormal rate?
Maybe it has to do with
the fact that the cells
in hair and nails are dead,
and they aren't reacting
in the same way.
On this beach, 60 minutes is two years.
We'll age almost 50 years in one day here.
Almost a lifetime.
I think it could be the rock
that surrounds this beach.
If our cells are being affected,
speeding up in their processes,
then us trying to leave
is like swimming to the surface too fast
after being deep in the ocean.
Our bodies can't reacclimate.
That's why we go unconscious
when we try to leave.
Maybe we could slowly
walk through the canyon,
take a step, stand still.
Do it over eight to ten hours.
Let our bodies acclimate.
But, according to Prisca's timeline,
who would be willing to give up
20 years of their life trying?
I'm sorry, this is nonsense.
Let's not shut down everyone's experience.
Wait. Where are the kids?
Trent!
Kara!
Answer us now! We need you here!
There they are.
- Want some?
- No, I'm not hungry.
Hey.
Mom! Dad!
Kara.
- What did you do?
- We were just playing.
It's okay. I just got a little fat.
Mom, you're better.
Maddox?
- Maddox?
- It's okay, Trent.
Just let Mom and Dad figure this out.
My God, Guy.
It's okay, right, Mom?
Jack Nicholson and Marlon Brando
were in a movie together.
If she walked into the emergency room,
I'd say she's about five months pregnant.
- What?
Just stay calm, Trent.
She'll only be pregnant for about
20 minutes from the time of conception.
Why do you keep looking at me
like you wanna steal my wallet?
- Do you want me to punch you in the face?
- Calm down.
- I have no idea what you're talking about.
- All right.
Let's just concentrate
on the issue at hand.
Do you know about movies?
Dad, Mom tells you to sit down
when you get like this.
Hey. We need to get her help. Okay?
- This cannot happen here.
- It's gotten bigger.
- Kara? It's Kara, right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Lay down on a blanket.
It's gonna be okay. There's
a lot of people here that can help you.
We're all like your family now.
Oh, God.
Ohh.
Our cells are aging very fast here.
Something to do with the rocks
around the beach, we think.
Just lay down on the sand, okay?
Whatever would have happened to us
is happening to us really fast, okay?
I know.
What you did is how babies are made.
I know, but I thought you had
to do that ten times or something.
- Take deep breaths. I'll breathe with you.
- Did I get that wrong?
- Baby, come on.
- It can happen after only once.
We didn't get a chance
to talk about all this.
- Are Trent and I having a baby?
- Did I get it wrong?
Only a couple of minutes left
if we're right.
- Is that the baby? Mom.
- You got it. Okay.
- Charles!
- Kara?
I need to think
about what to do.
No! I need to help her.
- Mom! I'm scared!
- It's okay.
- Kara, wait. Stay with me.
- I'm here, baby.
- Stay with me.
- Just take my hand.
Come on. Baby, can you hold her hand?
I've decided I'm gonna marry her.
And we are never gonna yell at each other
and we are never getting divorced!
Trent, listen to me.
She's going to feel pain. Intense pain.
Okay? Like she never felt before.
But then it's going to pass. Okay?
It's going to pass.
- You did it, girl!
- Mom!
- All right.
- Chrystal.
Chrystal!
Hey, you blacked out.
You can't go that way.
Come on. You're okay now.
Come on.
Get up. Get up.
- Come here.
- No.
Look.
You're okay. Come on. Come on.
- Babies crying helps them breathe.
- It's here.
We looked that up. Remember, Mom?
You see?
We put him on the towel
to clean him up.
He looked around and closed his eyes.
We had him on the towel for one minute.
He died from lack of attention.
Things are moving
too fast here for a baby to survive.
No. No, you're lying.
You're lying! You're all lying!
You're lying!
Shut up, Trent.
- Hey. Hey!
- You're lying!
Maybe we should all talk
about what just happened.
Charles, get us out of here!
Get us out of here now!
You were supposed to protect us!
You didn't protect us.
Kara's hurt!
I will make these decisions.
Just give me a second.
I used to see you in our neighborhood.
Who are you?
I'm Jarin!
I don't know where you live.
Don't condescend to me.
Put some makeup on your face.
I'm sorry about the baby.
When I was your age,
I was in love with a man.
His name was Giuseppe.
He wasn't very handsome,
and I left him.
We looked silly together, he and I.
He had nothing to offer.
For some reason,
I think about him a lot here.
Leave me alone.
- No, Charles!
- Stop!
Stop!
He's gone.
Oh, God.
I'm just going to take it.
- Now...
- It's okay.
Everything will be okay.
I'll find another beach
and I'll try to find help.
She needs her medicine.
We're lucky she hasn't had a seizure yet.
It must be the beach.
Whatever it's doing to my body.
Guy, I was on the swim team. I'll make it.
I'll make it.
Watch him.
Maybe I could climb that rock.
Maybe the effect, the blacking out,
doesn't happen if you go up.
You can't do it.
- I'll do it.
- Yeah, he's strong. He can do it.
- Yeah.
- No.
I won't allow my son to do that.
Prisca's right.
It's too dangerous.
It's a last resort.
Mum...
I do feel... overwhelmed.
I'm managing, but no one must know.
They'll try to stop me from working.
What should I do?
Mum, tell me what to do.
Prisca,
something's bothering me.
Charles's family knew he had
some kind of mental disorder.
Someone in each group was sick.
How did you first hear about this place?
I don't know. I fell upon it.
A random sweepstakes.
It came with a receipt at the pharmacy.
I just followed it up online,
started getting emails.
They know
our medical condition.
They chose us.
They have our passports.
We could just disappear.
They sent us a special car to the airport.
A plane.
They can make it look
like we never left the house.
You were thinking
about leaving Dad.
Weren't you?
Yes.
I didn't want you two to suffer.
Was there someone else?
Did Dad know?
Maddox.
Please.
I found out about this tumor
and I got scared.
I stare at the remains
of nameless people in glass cases
and I kept thinking
I'm going to be one of those people.
Does that make any sense?
I feel different than I felt yesterday.
What I did feels like an illusion,
I swear.
You hate me now.
I just need some time, Mom.
We don't have that, baby.
Look at you.
You're an adult.
Be strong for everyone.
Connect to something bigger.
Here, here, hold on.
Lay him down, lay him down.
He must have gone unconscious swimming.
Brendon didn't do anything to that woman.
We can't swim out, Prisca.
We're not getting off this beach.
We never had a prom,
or a graduation.
There are so many memories we didn't have.
It's not fair.
He needs to rest now.
Kara!
Wait. What if you get dizzy up there?
- You might black out.
- Trent, we're in charge now.
My dad could hurt more people.
I have to get him off this beach.
Kara! Don't climb that.
Come down! We'll find another way.
No! Don't! Trent!
- Listen to Mom.
- I have to go with her!
Kara, wait! Don't climb.
Let me get your mother.
- Kara!
- That's not the way.
She's panicked and desperate.
Talk to each other.
Kara, you and I
should just stay together.
What if we spend this whole time
trying to get out of here
and we still don't make it?
It'll be too short if we don't try.
No, Kara, please!
Please just stay with me, please!
If she makes it to the ledge,
she might have a chance.
Go to the ledge and rest!
Oh, shit.
There has to be a way out.
It's a mathematical certainty.
There must be a way out.
No. Why is she stopping?
No.
No, Kara.
Kara, wake up!
Kara, wake up! Wake up!
Oh!
Kara?
Daddy...
Let's all stay together.
Nobody in this family goes alone anywhere.
I think I figured it out.
I'm using these to swim out.
I have a sister.
She's a therapist, too.
I need to get to my sister.
We never talk.
We had a fight a long time ago.
She's older, but now I am.
The fighting seems ridiculous now.
Patricia.
No.
What's happening to her?
She was fine. What's happening?
She keeps stopping
and starting.
Dad, do something.
No.
Oh, no.
Kara?
Kara, where are you?
Somebody's done this to us, Kara.
I can't protect you anymore.
Kara!
No, you don't know.
Jarin went in a different way.
He went...
And I'm a better swimmer than he is.
He's older than me.
I could probably swim left...
Trent, stop it. No. No.
- No, you're not a better swimmer.
- Let me try.
- You're not even gonna let me try.
- Listen. Listen.
Listen.
- ...then I can get on the rock.
- We're not gonna let you.
Stop. It won't work.
I don't wanna give up.
I really don't wanna give up.
- We're not giving up.
- If you let me try...
My back.
I need my calcium.
Chrystal?
Chrystal, stay with us.
Don't look at me.
Prisca, I have to tell you something.
I saw your text messages one day.
He says romantic things.
I'm sorry.
I don't know who I would have been
okay with. But with that guy?
He's a joke, he's a pretend person.
You deserve someone
so much better than that.
I should have said something
when I saw it.
I hide from everything.
I'm a fucking coward.
This was no one's responsibility but me.
Your anger should be
aimed at me, just me.
There's no place I want to be
but with you.
Do you believe me?
I want to be here...
right now.
It's notebooks.
Well, maybe we can use some
of the empty pages for the fire,
keep Mom and Dad warm.
Whoever it was wanted
to be a science-fiction writer.
It's full of story ideas.
"Birds that can make you black out
when they scream,
fly too close to an Emirates
commercial plane one day."
He realized he was never getting off
this beach.
He was trying to figure out
what's going on.
"Magnetism of this exact spot on the Earth
with the rocks on this beach,
submerged beneath the ocean
for millions of years,
deposited with special minerals,
are causing our cells
to age at a rapid rate.
Are there other places like this?
Who found this place?"
Maybe we can make a metal tube
that we can get in
that stops the effects on our cells.
Like at a dentist's office when they put
a metal vest on us before an X-ray.
I mean, then we could just walk out
with it on us and...
We'll get dizzy at first, but slowly we'll
get used to it and we can leave, right?
Where are we gonna make a metal tube?
He wrote down a list of
all the names and the addresses
of the people with him on the beach.
Maddox, that's a camera.
They're recording us.
Why would they do this?
Oh, no.
Who is that?
Prisca, who is that?
You're gonna tell them what I did.
The man with the tattoos,
he was gonna steal things from my home.
Guy!
- Aah!
- No!
I can't let you tell them.
I'm a good doctor.
He was gonna follow us,
he was gonna steal things from our home.
Why don't you believe me?
I stopped him.
Tell me where the knife is, Prisca!
I keep having these thoughts.
Listen, they keep coming to me.
Don't tell anyone.
Prisca, hide the kids!
I'll protect you!
Yes.
Maddox!
Trent!
I need you two to go
and find somewhere to hide now!
Somewhere where someone can't find you.
I need you to go right now!
- Mom, what? Wait.
- And don't ask any questions!
Now, go! Hide!
Go!
Shh.
There's someone in here with us.
My body hurts to move.
I miss Giuseppe.
Don't look at me!
Turn off the light!
I don't wanna be seen!
Argh.
Kara's dead, isn't she?
Whoever did this killed her, didn't they?
Kara died.
But it was an accident.
Aah!
Don't look!
God, it's already healed
in the wrong position.
Turn off the light!
Turn the light off.
I'm chief medical officer of my hospital!
I am not gonna let you
take it away from me!
Argh.
It's rust.
It acts like poison
when it gets into your bloodstream.
I'm sorry you were on this beach.
But this is my family.
Dad, Mom,
you guys gotta stay hydrated.
Mom.
Are you warm enough?
♪ The cupid's an archer ♪
♪ His violent departure ♪
♪ Leaves us at the altar ♪
♪ Wounded, weak and ready to bleed ♪
♪ I'll wash away someday ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason to remain ♪
♪ I will remain ♪
Were we fighting about something?
We were.
Well, whatever it was,
I'm not mad anymore.
I can't remember.
Why did we want
to leave this beach?
So beautiful.
It doesn't matter.
It's funny.
I forget...
the word.
It's about my feelings for you.
I know.
- Dad?
- Dad.
Mom?
Oh, Mom.
We have about 13 hours left,
do you think?
Hmm.
We just got three days older
while you held my face.
Should we keep trying to get out?
I guess so.
Wanna make a sandcastle first?
I wonder if everybody
continues to feel like a kid
when they're our age or...
is it because we were kids yesterday?
Idlib sent me a message
I never decoded.
Yeah, we thought we were so smart.
Decode it.
Each symbol means a letter.
We thought we were like spies.
What was the big message?
What's it say?
The coral might protect us
from the effects of the rocks.
Maybe that's like our metal tube.
Maybe we're just making up
what we want to hear.
Maybe he heard
they took people to this beach.
Idlib heard something he shouldn't have.
He has no idea what it means,
but he knows it's bad.
He's trying to help us.
Wait.
I need to get something.
Both of them drowned.
For a second, I thought
they were gonna get through the coral.
I don't know how they suddenly thought
about going there.
Theo, are you sure
they didn't make it?
We can't have another incident.
Sidney, relax.
I watched for a minute and a half.
And the person who got through last year
ended up drowning anyway.
We're fine.
Final members of Trial 73 are deceased.
Observations complete.
Bringing drives back, returning to base.
All rooms for this trial
have been cleared.
Uh, home computer devices
have been wiped.
Three home computers
still waiting to be scrubbed.
Hello. Uh...
a moment of silence
for the members of Trial 73.
Thank you.
Um... I'll try not to be dramatic.
Because of this beach,
we have been able to save
hundreds of thousands of lives
with new medicines.
Before we're done, it will be millions.
As you know,
we do trials and fail constantly.
But not today.
Tell them, Sidney.
One of this cohort
was a woman with the epileptic seizures.
Her name was Patricia Carmichael.
She suffered debilitating seizures
her whole life.
Nothing could help her.
The medicine we gave her when she arrived
turned out to be the exact mixture.
She didn't have a seizure
for 8 hours and 17 minutes.
Sixteen and a half years.
We cured her of her epilepsy.
We'll now fast-track trials,
make that medicine
and share it with the whole world.
Every single person that needs it.
Nature made that beach exist for a reason.
Warren and Warren was meant to find it
on their research expedition.
We were meant to test medicines
in one day, instead of a lifetime.
Lots more work to be done, everyone.
Let's do what nature wanted us to do.
Mr. and Mrs. Brody will arrive
at 11:00 a.m.
with six non-targeted guests.
Joseph Brody has early-onset Parkinson's.
Florence Brody will be accompanying him.
I'm gonna be a broken record
about this, Nils.
We should separate
the pure medical subjects
from the mental illness subjects.
Our violent schizophrenic patient cost us
the data on our blood clot patient.
Sidney, I doubt we'll alter protocol
at this point,
but put it in a form
and submit it to Warren and Warren again.
How are you?
Those kids went home.
They don't matter.
I tell you which kids you can play with.
You have to trust me
and don't ask questions. Okay?
- Okay.
- Good.
Now, those kids are fine.
See, you can play with them.
- Okay.
- Good.
You're a police officer.
Yeah.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Brody.
Welcome to our version of paradise.
Thank you.
- It's lovely.
- Thank you.
This is Madrid.
From your food and beverage preferences
that you selected,
we've made you cocktails to welcome you.
- Sorry.
- No worries, Mr. and Mrs. Brody.
We'll just make a new set.
It'll only take a few moments.
I wouldn't take
anything they give you.
They left us all to die.
My name is Trent Capa.
I'm Maddox Capa.
All three are missing persons?
Sending you the rest of the names now.
Our parents
are Guy and Prisca Capa.
We live at 707 Pine Street,
Philadelphia, USA.
Also with us was Jarin Carmichael,
who was a nurse.
Listen, we have to get security.
What's happening?
Are you listening to me?
Gentlemen. Hey, hey, hey!
Gentlemen, we have a problem.
We need your assistance immediately.
Two of our guests need your attention.
Please solve this problem, now.
They've arrested everybody here.
Subpoenas are being served at Warren
and Warren's headquarters this week.
Let's get them to the airport.
Your aunt will be waiting for you
when you land.
How's she handling things?
How would you feel
if a 50-year-old man called and told you
he was your six-year-old nephew?
We'll be okay.
♪ Somewhere on the edge of sleep ♪
♪ There is a taste of peace ♪
♪ Every night we dance in my dreams ♪
♪ The cupid's an archer ♪
♪ His violent departure ♪
♪ Leaves us at the altar ♪
♪ Wounded, weak and ready to bleed ♪
♪ I'll wash away someday ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason ♪
♪ To remain ♪
♪ And I will remain ♪
♪ Through comfort and pain ♪
♪ Till I wash away ♪
♪ You are all that I can see ♪
♪ Alone I'm obsolete ♪
♪ Every flight is purgatory ♪
♪ Stripped of the armor ♪
♪ We plead and we barter ♪
♪ We stray from my harbor ♪
♪ Searching for some false remedy ♪
♪ I'll wash away someday ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason ♪
♪ To remain ♪
♪ And I will remain ♪
♪ Through comfort and pain ♪
♪ Till I wash away ♪
♪ I could never leave you ♪
♪ You are my first and last love ♪
♪ Every day I'm near you ♪
♪ I have enough ♪
♪ I'll wash away some day ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason ♪
♪ To remain ♪
♪ And I will remain ♪